#### Savannah Adams

Orlando, FL • Mobile: (863)-455-6688 • savannahmadams 02@gmail.com •

## **EXECUTIVE SUMMARY**

Passionate student at the University of Central Florida, with over 1 year of customer service and a desire to succeed in the business industry. Excels at conversing with other individuals due to strong communication skills. Pays close attention to detail to ensure mistakes are not made. Has computer competence and will be working towards certifications for different computer softwares.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### University of Central Florida, Orlando, FL

August 2020 - May 2023

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration, Real Estate

Cumulative GPA: 3.538

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

NNN Capital – Orlando, FL August 2021- Present

Junior Research Intern

- Provide research and analysis to support ongoing projects.
- Collected and entered in date into both REA and Excel.
- Worked closely with team members.

## 110TA Productions, Los Angeles, Ca

May 2021

**Background Actor** 

- Entertained audience members by consistently evoking strong emotions
- Maintained positive reputation in industry.

H & R Block - Lake Wales, FL

January 2019- March 2020

Client Service Professional

- Maintained meticulous electronic and physical filing systems with clients' records.
- Routed messages, coordinated appointments, and directed personnel to various departments.
- Answered questions regarding company pricing and policies.

### **Skills**

- Analytical thinking
- Community relations
- Problem solving
- Marketing
- Ability to negotiate

# **HONORS**

- Top 5% of graduating class, Lake Wales High School 2020.
- Dean's List, academic year 2020-2021 UCF.

## **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

Computer Skills: Microsoft Office, WordPress, Excel, REA

#### Extracurricular

- Member: Real Estate Club UCF
- Member: Best Buddies UCF
- Leader: Winter Springs Young Life
- Volunteer: Habitat for Humanity, Straight Street Inc., SALT Outreach